Guide to the University of Chicago, Yerkes Observatory, Office of the Director Records 1891-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: 1903-1946
  - U, 1946, University of Chicago fellowship University of Chicago Hutchins University of Chicago Council (Box 229, Folder 9)
  - U, 1946, University of Chicago Library University of Chicago (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Senate, 1946 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Univeristy of Chicago notices, 1946 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1946 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - U, 1946, University of Chicago Publicity University of Chicago Registrar University of Chicago Personnel University of Chicago 40" observing program Univeristy of Chicago colloquia University of Chicago reports (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Purchasing Agent, 1946 (Box 230, Folder 6-7)
  - A, 1947, Astrophysical Journal, Alexander Astrophysical Journal, bills Astrophysical Journal, budget (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Astrophysical Journal, reprint orders, 1947 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - A, 1947, Astrophysical Journal, Merrill Astrophysical Journal Astrophysical Journal, subscriptions (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - A, 1947, Abbott, W. N., 2 pages Abetti, R. A., 1 page Abetti, G., 3 pages Abrams, J. W., 6 pages Adams, W. S., 13 pages Adel, A., 5 pages Air Reduction Sales, 3 pages Alden, H. L., 2 pages Van Alhade, 1 page Allabada, G., 3 pages Aller, L. H., 13 pages Alter, D., 2 pages Amateur Astronomical Association, 5 pages American Association Advancement Science, 12 pages American Astronomical Society, 9 pages American Philosophical Society, 4 pages Argentina, San Miguel, 1 page Armitage, H., 2 pages Army Map Service, 7 pages Association Scientists for Atomic Education, 1 page Astronomical Society Pacific, 6 pages Athens National Observatory, Greece, 1 page Aziz, Abdulazim, 2 pages (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Applications, 1947 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - B, 1947, Babcock, H. W., 1 page Baker, R. H., 3 pages Barbier, M. D., 4 pages Barry, E. L., 2 pages Barton, R. F., 4 pages Bausch and Lomb, 1 page Becker, F., 2 pages Beer, E. A., 1 page Belgian-American Education Foundation, 2 pages Belgique, Observatory Royal, 1 page Belserene, E. P., 2 pages Benjamin Franklin Hotel, 1 page Bernstein, H. J., 1 page Biographical Encyclopedia of the World, 1 page Bird, D. M., 2 pages Blaauw, A., 7 pages Blanco, V., 1 page Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 15 pages Bok, B. J., 25 pages Bourgeois, D., 3 pages Bowen, I. S., 3 pages Bown, R., 4 pages Braun, W. C., 3 pages Breit, G., 1 page Encyclopaedia Britannica, 14 pages British Naval Supervisor, 2 pages Brouwer, Dirk, 7 pages Bruce, C. E., 3 pages Burnham Astronomical Society, 12 pages Burrows, C. R., 5 pages Buscher, J., 2 pages Bush, V., 2 pages (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - C, 1947, California Institute of Technology, 4 pages Calvert, M. R., 7 pages Carpenter, E. F., 3 pages Central Camera Company, 3 pages Chamberlin, R. T., 11 pages Chandrasekhar, S., 11 pages Chang, Y. C., 7 pages Chapin, A. V., 2 pages Chapman, E. N., 1 page Department of Chemistry, 1 page Chicago Academy of Sciences, 4 pages Chicago Astronomical Society, 4 pages Chun, 1 page Clark, Guy W., 2 pages Clearman, G. M., 1 page Clemence, 5 pages Connecticut Council Churches, 1 page Counsul General USSR, 2 pages Corning Glass Works, 3 pages Couderc, P., 1 page Cowling, T. G., 1 page Crew, Henry, 5 pages (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - D-E, 1947, Daro, Simone, 2 pages deGroot, S. R., 2 pages Deutsch, Armin, 6 pages DeVany, A., 2 pages Delavan Shopper, 2 pages Dieke, G. H., 2 pages Dodson, Helen W., 2 pages Donn, B., 2 pages Dornberger, W., 2 pages Downing, Mrs. E., 9 pages Duff, H. E., 1 page Duke, Douglas, 1 page Duncan, J. C., 2 pages Dunham, T., 2 pages DuPont, 1 page Durand, E., 1 page Royal Dutch Airlines, 1 page Eastman Kodak, 26 pages Edmondson, F. K., 21 pages Egge, O. J., 2 pages Elbert, W. L., 3 pages Elvey, C. T., 3 pages Engelhardt Astronomical Observatory, 1 page English, Henry W., 2 pages Erro, L. E., 2 pages Express Publishing Company, 1 page (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - F, 1946, Fauth, H., 2 pages Federer, Mrs. C. A., 1 page Fensholt, O. B., 2 pages Fischer, Clyde, 2 pages E. R. Flint and Company, 3 pages Fortune Magazine, January 47 article on astrophysics, 4 pages France, St. Michel Observatory, 1 page Franck, James, 1 page French Naval Attache, 2 pages First National Bank (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - G, 1946, Gaertner Scientific, 1 page Gaposchkin, C. P., 9 pages Gaposchkin, S., 8 pages Gardner, A. F., 2 pages Gauzit, J., 2 pages Geneva Lake Property Owners, 8 pages Gibbs Division, 1 page Giclas, 1 page Gingrich, C. H., 22 pages Goldberg, Leo, 30 pages Gollnow, H., 4 pages Golub, N., 6 pages Goshen College, 2 pages Greenstein, J. L., 28 pages Griffith Observatory, 1 page Grincyenko, H., 2 pages Lake Geneva Water Power and Lake Level, 4 pages (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - H, 1947, Hall, J. S., 2 pages Hall, R. G., 1 page Halla, F., 1 page Hamburger Sternwarte, 1 page Hardie, R., 3 pages Harris, Dan, 3 pages Harvard College Observatory, 2 pages Hawkins, Helen W., 1 page Heckmann, O., 4 pages Hemminger, E., 3 pages Henyey, L., 2 pages Herget, P., 2 pages Hertzsprung, E., 4 pages Herzberg, G., 7 pages Herzog, E., 7 pages Hetzler, R., 2 pages Heyden, F. J., 1 page Heyduck, C., 3 pages Heyman, L., 1 page Hickman, J. E., 1 page Hiltner, W. A., 56 pages Hoag, A. A., 5 pages Hodges, P. C., 3 pages Houston Chronicle, 1 page Houtermans, F. G., 1 page Huffer, C. M., 41 pages Hulburt, E. O., 2 pages Hylleraas, E. A., 1 page Hynek, J. A., 11 pages (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - I-J, 1947, International Astronomical Union, 20 pages Ice Herschel, 3 pages Illinois Bell, 1 page International News Service, 2 pages International Students’ Association, 1 page Ipatieff, P., 1 page Irwin, J. B., 3 pages Jablonski, A., 1 page Jackson, J., 1 page James, D. O., Geares, 11 pages James Manufacturing Company, 1 page Janesville Gazette, 1 page Janssen, Edith, 8 pages Jassy, Mathematical Institute, 2 pages Johns Hopkins Univeristy, 5 pages Johnson, A. E., 2 pages Johnson, C. F., 2 pages Jones, H. Spencer, 4 pages Jones, Rufus M., 2 pages Jose, Paul B., 12 pages Joy, A. H., 2 pages (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Kuiper, 109 pages, 1947 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - K-L, 1947, Kansas State College, 2 pages Keenan, P. C., 10 pages Kienle, H., 1 page Kieperhauer, K. U., 5 pages Kiev Observatory, 1 page Kluyver, H. A., 2 pages Koopmans, T. C., 1 page Kopal, Z., 2 pages Kopff, A., 5 pages Krause, H., 2 pages Kreiken, E. A., 2 pages Krogdahl, M. K., 2 pages Krogdahl, Wasley, 2 pages Krug, E., 1 page Kuiper, N. H., 2 pages Lake Geneva Water Power, 4 pages Geneva Lake Property Owners Association, 1 page Lampland, C. O., 2 pages Leclaire, R., 1 page Ledoux, A., 1 page Lee, O. J., 19 pages Leighton, W., 3 pages Leland, S. E., 3 pages Leonard, F. C., 1 page Levitt, I. M., 7 pages Levy, Lisbon, 2 pages Lindblad, B., 2 pages Link, G. K. K., 1 page Linnik, 2 pages Lucht, V. M., 1 page Luyten, W. T., 8 pages Lyot, B., 9 pages (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - M, 1947, McCuskey, S. W., 4 pages McLaughlin, D. B., 3 pages McLeod, Noah W., 1 page McMath, R. R., 4 pages Macmillan Company, 4 pages Madrid Observatory, Torroja, 1 page Marchant, 1 page Mario, M., 2 pages Markov, A., 2 pages Markowitz, W., 6 pages Marquis Publishing, 1 page Marshak, R. A., 1 page Marinetz, W., 2 pages Mather, K. B., 3 pages Mayall, N. U., 1 page Menzel, D. H., 4 pages Merrill, P. W., 1 page Society Astronomic de Mexico, 1 page Migeotte, M., 3 pages Mikhailov, A., 1 page Miller, W., 3 pages Millis, John, 7 pages Milwaukee Journal, 1 page Minnaert, M., 13 pages Minneapolis Morning Tribune, 2 pages Missouri Pacific Lines, 20 pages Mitchell, S. A., 3 pages Monk, G., 8 pages Observatorio Astronomioo de Montevideo, 2 pages Moore, J. H., 2 pages Moreton, G. E., 1 page Morgan, G. D., 8 pages Morris, Don, 1 page Morrison Hotel, 1 page Van de Mortel, J. B. V. M. J., 2 pages Motor Transport, 1 page Moulton, F. R., 1 page Munch, G., 5 pages Mulliken, R. S., 3 pages Munnecke, W. G., 3 pages (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - McDonald Observatory, power plans, 1947 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - McDonald Observatory, 1947 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - N-O, 1947, Nassau, J. J., 9 pages National Academy of Sciences, 24 pages National Cylinder Gas Company, 1 page National Technical Laboratories, 1 page Naval Ordnance Lab, 4 pages Nekrassoff, V. A., 2 pages Nelson’s Encyclopedia, 1 page Nicolet, M., 2 pages Nicholson, S. B., 4 pages Nielson, Niels, 3 pages Norrmann, E., 3 pages Northwestern University, 1 page Observatory, 1 page Olivier, C. P., 2 pages Oort, J. H., 22 pages Opik, E., 2 pages Oppenheimer, H. D., 3 pages Optical Works Limited, 3 pages Orlov, B., 1 page (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - P, 1947, Page, T. L., 39 pages Painter, T. S., 8 pages Parsons, J. B., 2 pages Pawsey, J. L., 3 pages Pearce, J. A., 2 pages Pearson, 1 page Penguin Books, 1 page Perry, W. H., 1 page Peterson, J. M., 1 page Phemister, D. B., 1 page Photographic Supply Department, 2 pages Physikalische Anstalt, University Basel, 2 pages Pierce, N. L., 5 pages Pillans, H., 3 pages Pioneer Sceintific Corporation, 1 page Planck, M., 1 page Plaskett, H. H., 1 page National Plastics Exposition, 2 pages Platt, J. R., 5 pages Pohl, N. W., 2 pages Polytechnic Institute Astronomy, Poland, 1 page Popper, D. M., 13 pages Porter, H. H., 1 page Prentice, J. R., 1 page Price, W. C., 2 pages (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - P-Q, 1947, Paradox Questions (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Questions, 1947 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - R, 1947, Radio Corporation of America, 1 page Raimond, J. J., 3 pages Raju, M. K., 4 pages Reber, G., 5 pages Recillas, P. P., 16 pages Reilly, E. F., 2 pages Remington Rand, 2 pages Rice Institute, 3 pages Riggs, R. S., 2 pages Roach, F. E., 1 page Roberts, J. L., 2 pages Rockford College, 5 pages Rosebrugh, D. W., 4 pages Royal Astronomical Society, 2 pages Russell, H. N., 15 pages Rymer, H. R., 3 pages (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - S, 1947, Shapley, 26 pages Struve (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - S, 1947, Saha, M. N., 2 pages Sahade, J., 7 pages Salisbury, W. W., 3 pages Sanborn, H. D., 1 page University of Saskatchewan, 1 page Schilt, Jan, 3 pages Schoenberg, E., 2 pages Schoonmaker, W., 5 pages Science, 25 pages Science Illustrated, 6 pages Science Service, 5 pages Scobee, B., 1 page Seeger, C. L., 2 pages Sen, H. K., 7 pages Severny, A. B., 3 pages Shajn, G., 24 pages Shane, C. D., 4 pages Shapley, A. H., 1 page Shatzel, A. V., 1 page Shneiderov, A. J., 18 pages Sigma Xi, 7 pages Simmons, C. D., 7 pages (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - S, 1947, Slocum, Lois T., 1 page Smith, Burke, 9 pages Smithsonian Institute, 16 pages Snyder, Hartland S., 3 pages Spangenberg, Karl, 1 page Spitzer, Lyman, 24 pages Sproul Observatory, 4 pages Stalnaker, L. N., 2 pages Stebbins, Joel, 26 pages Stechert-Hafner, 2 pages Steinmetz, C. H. D., 1 page John Stocks Travel Service, 5 pages Strand, K. A., 8 pages Stratton, F. J. M., 3 pages Streeter, John, 4 pages Stromgren, B., 17 pages Stromgren, E., 2 pages Subbotin, M., 2 pages Sul Ross State Teachers College, 3 pages Swensson, John, 2 pages Swings, P., 81 pages (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - S-U, 1947, Symposium Planetary Atmospheres, 2 pages Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1 page Telechron Incorporated, 5 pages Texas Academy of Science, 2 pages Texas State Parks Board, 2 pages University of Texas, 4 pages Thackeray, A. D., 2 pages Thomas, A. R., 2 pages Thorndyke, A., 2 pages Tikhov, G. A., 3 pages Torroja, J. M., 1 page Tosi, F., 1 page Travel Bureau, 1 page Chicago Tribune, 7 pages Trumpler, R. J., 7 pages Board of Trustees, 1 page Tuominen, J., 7 pages Underhill, A., 5 pages United States Civil Service Committee, 8 pages United States Department of Justice, 1 page Committee for US Information Abroad, 1 page United States Naval Observatory, 3 pages United States Post Office, 12 pages United Transformer Corporation, 3 pages Unsold, A., 3 pages (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - V-Z, 1947, Valentine, W. L., 6 pages Valley View Observatory, 1 page Van, 1 page Van Albada, G. B., 1 page Van Allen, J. A., 2 pages Van Biesbroeck, G., 8 pages V. Bueren, H. G., 2 pages Van de Hulst, H. C., 9 pages Van de Kamp, P., 1 page Vanderlinden, H. L., 1 page Vandien, Elsa, 7 pages Van Hoof, 2 pages Van Klooster, H. S., 1 page Van Rhyn, P. J., 2 pages deVany, A., 2 pages Vassar College, 2 pages Velghe, A., 1 page Vosatka, 1 page Wares, G., 1 page Weaver, H. F., 8 pages Western Union, 2 pages Whipple, F. L., 10 pages Whitney, B. S., 6 pages Wildt, R., 1 page Williams Bay, 4 pages Williamson, R. E., 1 page Wisconsin Power and Light, 1 page Wisconsin Southern Gas, 3 pages Wisconsin Telephone Company, 1 page Witkowski, J., 2 pages Wood, D. L., 1 page Wood, F. B., 1 page Wright, K. O., 11 pages Wright, Quincy, 2 pages Wrubel, M., 2 pages Wurm, K., 3 pages Wylie, C. C., 8 pages Yamamoto, I., 2 pages Zachariasen, W., 1 page (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, electric bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses, 1947 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago Bursar University of Chicago Business Manager (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, 1947 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, petty cash, Yerkes, 1947 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago Comptroller, payroll, Yerkes University of Chicago Comptroller, petty cash, McDonald University of Chicago Comptroller, bills charged McDonald (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, payroll, McDonald (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Division Dean, 1947 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Division, 1947 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago fellowships University of Chicago Hutchins (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Senate, 1947 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago Library University of Chicago University of Chicago notices (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago President’s Office University of Chicago Press (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Publicity, 1947 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Purchasing Agent, 1947 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - U, 1947, University of Chicago Registrar University of Chicago colloquia University of Chicago observing 40" University of Chicago reports of work (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago reports, 1947 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago requisitions, 1947 (Box 236, Folder 7)
- Series III: McDonald Observatory
  - Adams, Walter S., correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Alpine Lumber Company, correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Applications for positions at McDonald observatory, correspondence, 1933-1936 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Astronomical equipment, aluminization vacuum chamber, for coating astronomical mirrors by evaporation, correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Astronomical equipment, Coude spectrograph glasses, correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Astronomical equipment, Coude 3-prism, mounting details, blueprints, sketches, graphs, notes and correspondence, 1934- 1935 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Astronomical equipment, filar micrometer eye pieces, Hale spectrohelioscope, correspondence and notes, 1935-1936 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Astronomical equipment, quartz prisms and spectrograph lenses, correspondence and notes, 1934-1935 (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - Astronomical equipment, Slitless spectrograph, Schmidt telescope and camera, correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - Astronomical equipment, notes, undated (Box 237, Folder 10)
  - Bhade, Walter, correspondence, 1932 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Benedict, H. Y., President of the University of Texas, planning and preparation for McDonald Observatory, correspondence, 1932- 1937 (Box 238, Folder 2-8)
  - Bids for construction and employment at McDonald Observatory, correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 239, Folder 1-2)
  - Calhoun, J. W., Comptroller University of Texas, correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 239, Folder 3-4)
  - Comrie, L. J., correspondence, 1932 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Contracts, drafts, suggested changes, and correspondence, 1932- 1939 (Box 239, Folder 6-7)
  - Corning Glass Works, correspondence, 1929-1934 (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, correspondence and notes, 1937-1939 (Box 240, Folder 1-4)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, invitations, correspondence, 1939 (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, local invitations, correspondence, 1939 (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, planning the schedule of events, correspondence and notes, 1938-1939 (Box 240, Folder 7)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, publicity, publication of symposium papers, correspondence, 1939 (Box 240, Folder 8)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, symposium papers and abstracts, 1939 (Box 240, Folder 9)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, publicity, press releases and correspondence, 1939 (Box 240, Folder 10-11)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, packet with comprehensive plans for guest lists, meals, itineraries, transportation, and programs, 1939 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, publicity, correspondence, 1939 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, publicity, newspaper clippings, 1939 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Dedication ceremony for McDonald Observatory and symposium on modern astronomy, thank you correspondence, 1939 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Dornberger, W. W., Office of the Supervising Architect, University of Texas, correspondence and blueprints, 1933-1935 (Box 241, Folder 5-8)
  - Dornberger, W. W., Office of the Supervising Architect, University of Texas, correspondence and blueprints, 1935-1939 (Box 242, Folder 1-6)
  - Elvey, C. T., correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 242, Folder 7-8)
  - Elvey, C. T., correspondence, 1936-1938 (Box 243, Folder 1-7)
  - Elvey, C. T., correspondence, 1939 (Box 244, Folder 1-3)
  - Expense accounts, correspondence and receipts, 1934-1937 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Fecker, J. W., correspondence, 1932 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Fish-Schurman, correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - G-, correspondence, 1932 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - Hale, George E., correspondence, 1932 (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., President of the University of Chicago, correspondence, 1932-1937 (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - Houses and other auxillary structures, blueprints and correspondence, 1934 (Box 245, Folder 1-2)
  - Insurance, correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 245, Folder 3-4)
  - Mellish, John, correspondence, 1935-1936 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Miller, W. S., correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Mount Locke, Texas, correspondence, 1932-1938 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Morelock, H. W., President of Sull Ross State Teachers College, Alpine, Texas, correspondence, 1932-1937 (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Nicholson, C. H., correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Office of the Comptroller, University of Texas, McDonald expenditures, invoices, receipts, purchase orders and correspondence, 1934-1937 (Box 246, Folder 1-7)
  - Office of the Comptroller, University of Texas, McDonald expenditures, invoices, receipts, purchase orders and correspondence, 1938-1940 (Box 247, Folder 1-6)
  - Pamphlet for McDonald Observatory, correspondence, 1938 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - Plaskett, J. S., Director, Dominion Astrophysical Observatory, correspondence, 1933 (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - Power plant bids and estimates, correspondence, 1933 (Box 247, Folder 9)
  - Prism reimbursement for damage during transport with Railway Express Agency, correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 247, Folder 10)
  - Publications, exchange of, correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Publicity, press releases and correspondence, 1932-1937 (Box 248, Folder 2-3)
  - Publicity, newspaper clippings, 1932-1938 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Regents, Board of, minutes and correspondence, 1933-1939 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Roach, Franklin E., correspondence, 1932-1938 (Box 248, Folder 6-8)
  - R-S, correspondence, 1932-1937 (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - Records of the University of Texas Auditor’s Office for the W. J. McDonald fund for construction at the Yerkes Observatory shop of the attachments for the McDonald Telescope, balance sheets, 1933-1940 (Box 248, Folder 10)
  - Stark, H. J. Lutcher, correspondence, 1933-1936 (Box 248, Folder 11)
  - Texas, Jeff Davis County Chamber of Commerce, correspondence, 1932 (Box 248, Folder 12)
  - Tallmadge, T. E., correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Truck registration and insurance, correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, Board of, W. J. McDonald Astronomical Observatory, meeting minutes, 1939 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Telescope shipment, correspondence and notes, 1939 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - United States Government departments, correspondence and booklets, 1931-1933 (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, Weather Bureau, observer’s record, weather reports, 1932-1938 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Van Biesbroeck, G., correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Vaurie, J., correspondence, 1932 (Box 249, Folder 8)
  - Vyssotsky, A. N., correspondence, 1936-1938 (Box 249, Folder 9)
  - Warner and Swasey Company, correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 250, Folder 1-9)
  - Warner and Swasey Company, correspondence, 1936-1939 (Box 251, Folder 1-9)
  - Wood, R. W., correspondence, 1939 (Box 251, Folder 10)